(The second commercial district)
(Street Beer Festival)
(Two teams compete with the same price.)
(One team closes its business.)
(First half, Kim Kwan Hoon versus Lee Yeon Bok)
(BokBok wins.)
(Orders start flowing in as soon as the second half starts.)
(BokBok is sold out due to running out of ingredients.)
(Everything About Tteokbokki begins a fierce comeback.)
We have nothing left to sell while they'll keep getting orders.
Everything About Tteokbokki...
(Taking the lead by 60 dollars)
- What will be the result?
- I can't wait to find out.
(Lee Yeon Bok versus Kim Kwan Hoon)
- Everything About Tteokbokki.
- Well done.
BokBok.
(The match between the ultimate champions)
In the 2nd half of the 20-dollar price range...
(The second half result to determine the winner)
BokBok.
Everything About Tteokbokki.
Their sales are the same.
(Their sales are the same.)
How is that possible?
Their sales are the same?
I thought that we lost the second half.
I couldn't understand.
(Right before the end of the second half)
(Everything About Tteokbokki was taking the lead by 60 dollars.)
While we were winning, when I glanced at Lee Yeon Bok,
he was cleaning up.
So I thought, "All right, we won."
We didn't get our order yet.
- Is it possible to cancel it?
- Yes, you can cancel it. I'm sorry.
(A refund customer appears.)
(The second refund customer appears.)
(Refunds start coming in one after the other.)
(Someone didn't take their order.)
(And there was a third refund.)
(Currently, their sales are the same.)
It was a bummer.
Their sales are the same. They're tied.
It'll be decided by customer ratings.
This is so nerve-racking.
I'll announce the customer ratings.
BokBok.
(BokBok, 2nd half sales: 840 dollars)
Four points.
(Customer ratings: 4 points)
Everything About Tteokbokki.
(Everything About Tteokbokki, 2nd half sales: 840 dollars)
It's 3.7 points.
(Customer ratings: 3.7 points)
- With a difference of 0.3 points, - That was close.
BokBok wins.
(BokBok is the final winner with 2 to 0.)
The final winner in the 20-dollar price range is BokBok.
- Well done.
I hope that you win.
- I'm sorry.
- Please win for us.
Well done, everyone.
This experience taught me...
a huge lesson all over again.
It really reminded me just how important ratings are.
Next time, we'll have to come up with a better strategy.
We would've won if the two bowls hadn't been canceled.
- We gave it everything we had.
- We did our best.
(Everything About Tteokbokki, BokBok)
More than anything,
even though we lost, we fought a good battle.
I don't have any regrets.
We did an amazing job, especially under those circumstances.
It was a tough challenge, but we worked together well...
and gave it our best.
That's what I kept thinking.
(Today's matchup continues.)
(1-on-1 same price battle)
The matchup I was most curious about was...
Gotgan that makes Korean food...
Gotgan and The Star In My Heart.
When Chef Jo Seo Hyung picked Gotgan,
I thought that it'd be really fun.
(1-on-1 same price battle, The Star In My Heart)
(The Star In My Heart picked Gotgan.)
I knew it.
- They're true rivals.
- This will be fun.
It's a derby.
A Korean cuisine derby.
A true Korean food showdown.
I want to have a fun dance with Korean food.
(Laughing)
I'm very happy...
that she chose us. I like how bold she is.
Let's go for a head-to-head fight.
I've been cooking Korean food for a long time,
but the elder ladies' seasoning,
balance, and homemade touch...
That territory is intimidating.
(Gotgan, led by the original Imokase)
So I was intimidated.
If it's a mountain I have to climb someday,
I might as well climb it sooner than later.
Chef Jo Seo Hyung has been in this business for a long time,
but I've been doing it longer.
I'll do my best to rise to the challenge.
In the ten-dollar range, The Star In My Heart versus Gotgan.
- The Star In My Heart.
- This is a big match.
(Who will be the winner of the Korean food showdown?)
Let's put this out first.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
- They're taking out the equipment.
- They prepared a lot.
We almost made that too, but we couldn't be bothered.
(It's a nice day to cook.)
Don't block the storefront.
- Should I put it here?
- Yes.
What do you call it? We made a flyer.
- No, we made banners.
- We made banners.
(Gotgan prepared eye-catching banners.)
Putting my photo on it...
with big texts helped it stand out.
(It's a nice day to cook.)
(A menu that makes you crave beer?)
Just because I cook Korean food doesn't mean...
that I only serve set meals.
This is a beer festival.
So I wanted to serve food that goes well with beer.
For the first half, we're serving fried suyuk and fried pork skin.
She has a big container. Should I ask if I can borrow it?
- Should I ask her for it?
- From where?
- The stall next door.
- No way.
Why not?
Chef Jo.
Are you not using that white kimchi container?
Mom, we don't need any kimchi container.
I want to keep the batter in it.
Don't borrow it from her.
We'll figure out our own way.
Why would you borrow from the team we're competing with?
I'm the type of person...
who can't sleep...
if I lose a competition like this.
What's wrong with borrowing it? She's not using it.
We have to beat the stall next door.
- I know.
- If we lose,
I won't be able to sleep.
(Gotgan is determined to win today.)
When I did the math,
I realized we'd have to fry well over...
a thousand bite-sized pieces of pork skin.
Mom, the oil is ready. We have to deep-fry all of these.
(Five ingredients to deep-fry)
(All ingredients are partially fried in advance.)
(Fried suyuk)
Ginseng won't take long. I'm so relieved.
It's done. It's going well.
Gosh, it looks nice.
Mom, we can keep doing it that way.
Is this enough?
Gosh, you prepared a lot.
Here you go.
Is everything boiling nicely?
The frying is going well so far.
I can smell your delicious food all the way over here.
- I want a piece of your fried food.
- We want some fried food.
I guess everyone is thinking the same thing.
- Since it's a festival...
- Fried food.
(Fried food)
(10 out of 18 teams are preparing fried food.)
It looks like everyone is frying something today.
- Jae Beom.
- Yes?
Please stir-fry the meat first.
Okay.
Great. It's a chance to add more smoky flavor.
For the first half, we're serving...
a mountain of spicy stir-fried pork and gimbap.
When I thought about what everyone else would make,
I didn't think many would go with rice dishes.
Most customers coming around 5pm will...
probably want something...
that works as a meal and a snack to go with beer.
That's where I knew we had a chance.
(Targeting a niche market with a rice-based dish)
I was wondering why it was so spicy.
I realized there was Cheongyang chili on one side.
- Smoky flavor is what I wanted.
- Smoky flavor.
(Preparing a spicy dish to cut through the heavy fried food)
It smells so delicious.
(Seasonal perilla sprouts, sesame seeds,)
(spicy stir-fried pork, gimbap)
(A mountain of spicy stir-fried pork and sesame gimbap for 10 dollars)
Chef?
We have 77 rolls so far.
Seventy-seven rolls.
That's exactly what we expected.
(Exchanging looks)
Come here for a second.
- What?
- Seventy-seven rolls?
- That means 77 servings.
- Yes.
We can make up to 120 servings.
In that case...
We could beat them with quantity as long as we sell them.
That's what I kept thinking.
(They can also see the other side.)
This might overflow.
You're preparing so much meat.
How many servings is that?
(Pretending not to notice)
That's enough for 200 people.
(Remaining silent)
What if they're preparing 150 servings?
Why are they making so much food?
(Street Arena)
Round 2 of 1-on-1 same price battle,
the first half will start now.
(1-on-1 same price battle business starts.)
Good luck, Chef Kim.
Good luck to you.
Good luck.
Let's do our best.
Let's start from there.
The 1st half and the 2nd half menu are...
- different.
- I see.
This is amazing. It looks very fun.
Everything looks delicious.
What should we order?
(Korean food showdown, Kim Mi Ryeong versus Jo Seo Hyung)
(Fried suyuk and pork skin versus a mountain...)
(of spicy stir-fried pork and sesame gimbap)
(Lee Jun Seong at Gotgan is waiting for customers.)
Gosh, it's so empty.
The stall next to us had a lot of decoration.
It feels so empty because we don't have much set up.
Wait, it's way too empty.
Mom.
- This won't work.
- What?
It's too empty.
Fill the empty spot with cutlassfish.
We put out the boneless cutlassfish we had prepared for dinner.
It fills up the space and...
- And it works as promotion.
- We're making this for dinner.
Instead of going somewhere else, come and have this for dinner.
It could give them a reason to come back.
Gosh, it's Imokase.
- My gosh.
- The 1st 60 people?
The 1st 60 people?
We're offering complimentary fried ginseng to the 1st 60 customers.
(Fried ginseng prepared by Imokase to the 1st 60 people)
By the way, the booth next door...
is giving out fried ginseng.
- Fried ginseng?
- On a 1st-come, 1st-served basis.
I don't think they can manage it at that price.
(They bought ginseng at a cheap price.)
(Ginseng, 75 dollars)
They were cull ginseng.
(Cull ginseng: Set aside due to its ugly appearance or blemishes)
(The taste and nutritional values remain the same.)
In Gyeongdong Market, they sell cull ginseng...
at a very cheap price, even for ginseng.
Most Koreans like ginseng.
Do you still have fried ginseng?
Yes, we do.
You'd better be quick. Did you place your order?
Don't leave. It'll be ready soon.
It's fried ginseng.
Fried ginseng?
(Gotgan's first order)
I got it.
Coming right away.
Like glutinous rice tangsuyuk, it's chewy outside...
and soft and juicy on the inside.
If you boil and then deep-fry the pork skin,
it becomes very soft and crispy.
(Fried suyuk and pork skin)
- Here it is. Add some sauce.
- Okay.
I intended them to go well with the soy sauce...
when I cooked them.
Enjoy.
Try it with the gochujang butter sauce too.
- Gochujang cream sauce.
You can taste 2 flavors in 1 dish.
Wait, take the ginseng with you.
Ginseng.
I'll place the ginseng here.
I've wanted to try this.
It's ten dollars.
It only costs ten dollars. Why is it so cheap?
- It's only ten dollars.
- I know, right?
Enjoy the food.
Hello.
Be the first to try.
(Gotgan, The Star In My Heart)
Have some gimbap.
Hello.
(The queue for the booth next to them)
Come over here now.
(Empty on this side)
Hello.
- Gimbap and spicy stir-fried pork.
- Hello.
Hello.
Selling gimbap at a beer festival won't be easy.
Exactly. Gimbap is too filling to go with beer.
Yes.
Let's order some fritters first.
Imokase's dish is pretty good.
- I want to drink the beer myself.
- This is bad.
Did we choose the wrong menu?
I could only think about one thing.
"Let's prove..."
"I didn't make a wrong decision."
I thought, "I'll make them queue in front of my booth."
I'm more than ready.
Whatever. I'll throw away my pride today.
What's in every man's heart?
- Spicy stir-fried pork.
- Gosh, you're so pretty.
- Goodness.
How could you say no to gimbap and perilla sprouts?
- It's only ten dollars.
- She knows the right things to say.
You're on the fence? Then come here.
Try it.
- Evaluate it as a man.
- It's so delicious.
(She even lets them taste it.)
How is it?
See? It's different.
- You're back.
- I'll order it.
This is crazy. Come here.
- Guys, it's spicy stir-fried pork.
- Do I pay here?
Yes. Pay here...
and come over with a tray.
Pay and come to me with a tray.
Come again if you want more.
- We'll give you more.
- You can have more.
We have spicy stir-fried pork and gimbap.
I'll give you a lot of spicy stir-fried pork.
We serve you warm spicy stir-fried pork right away.
Imokase's restaurant is an open kitchen,
and so is ours.
So we know better than anyone what the customers like.
They're very good...
- at attracting customers.
- They really are.
How many chopsticks do you need? Two?
What about you?
Three.
(Current sales: Only 70 dollars difference)
It's cauldron-cooked spicy stir-fried pork. Hello.
- Men love spicy stir-fried pork.
- Spicy stir-fried pork.
Men love suyuk.
Men don't love suyuk.
They love spicy stir-fried pork.
- Women love...
- Men love...
- ginseng.
- Men love spicy stir-fried pork.
- Spicy stir-fried pork and gimbap.
- It's super delicious.
- It's so good.
- It's amazing?
It's super good, right?
- You beat Imokase.
- It's good.
Really? He says we beat Imokase.
We did it.
He says our spicy stir-fried pork is better than Imokase's food.
Really?
- What will you do?
- He really said that?
Gosh, why would she say that?
I started getting more competitive in the kitchen.
I wasn't bothered at all. I'm not someone...
to be swayed by such words.
I found them rather cute.
Hello.
I was by far more confident.
Number 5417.
- Did I make it for the ginseng?
- Yes. It's right here!
Thank you.
When customers open the door to my restaurant and walk in,
you must see them as welcome guests to your home,
not as your restaurant's profits.
That's what I think business is.
- Can I have a lot of green onions?
- Of course, I'll give you lots.
Enjoy. I'll give you one more ginseng each.
(Cheering)
This is what Imokase is about, right?
(Comes with her experience of doing business in a market)
Come here quickly.
- Come on, Miss Jo.
- Come here quickly.
This is how you attract customers.
You're a true businessperson if you can capture their hearts.
Hello.
Go on and place the order.
Incheon National University.
I'll give you double the amount of spicy stir-fried pork.
Double the amount. Make some noise!
Thank you.
Eat up and spread the word.
Thank you. Spicy stir-fried pork. Come here.
Have it with perilla sprouts. Chopsticks are there.
Here, enjoy. Have it with the sauce.
- Enjoy the food.
- Thank you.
May I have your attention, please?
You are here as the on-site judging panel.
Please make sure to leave the review of the food you're eating.
How many stars out of five?
How many stars will you rate it?
What's the rating for Gotgan?
- Gotgan... It isn't bad, but...
- Out of ten?
- The portion is...
- I think the meat was a bit dry.
It's lightly-fried suyuk.
(Enigmatic expression)
- How much is this?
- Ten dollars.
If it's deep-fried, it should either be warm or crispy.
It's gone stale.
It got cold.
It got quite cold. I think I collected it a bit late.
(Many say fried suyuk has gone cold.)
We worried a lot about the ratings because of the suyuk.
(Since it had to be mass-produced, they had deep-fried it in advance.)
(Gotgan's food is evaluated rather poorly.)
For the first half,
we would win.
To keep it from going cold,
we put spicy stir-fried pork in a cauldron.
Yes, place it on top of it.
(The cauldron keeps it warm.)
Out of the three dishes, spicy stir-fried pork is the best.
- Me too.
- If I'm being honest.
Spicy stir-fried pork is crazy good.
The only food I rated five stars is spicy stir-fried pork.
Come and have spicy stir-fried pork and gimbap.
It's a perfect pair for beer.
I guess time is almost up.
May I have your attention, please?
- After five minutes, - Gosh, spicy stir-fried pork is...
all restaurants will stop accepting orders temporarily.
(There will be a performance during the break...)
(after the first half.)
How many do we have left?
Are we done if we sell 11 more?
Yes, I changed the status to sold out.
It's sold out. I'm sorry.
You can't order anymore. It's sold out.
You can't pay. It's sold out.
Two, three, four. Until here.
- I'm sorry.
- Mom, six more from now.
(Six more from now.)
Six people can order chicken breasts.
Chicken breasts.
It looked like we were neck and neck.
It wouldn't be an easy battle.
This won't do.
I thought to buy more ingredients to sell more,
so I ran to the market.
I'll buy one pack.
(Chicken breast, 500g, 6.20 dollars)
Since I already had the batter,
I made some boneless fried chicken using chicken breasts.
(Menu added last-minute: Fried chicken breast)
- You can refill. Bring your plate.
- The first half of the business...
- Wait for a bit. I'll call you.
- ends in ten seconds.
- Ten. Nine.
- Sesame gimbap.
Eight.
- Seven.
- Six more.
- Six.
- Six?
- Five.
- Yes.
Four, three, two, one.
The first half of the business has ended.
(The first half of the business ends.)
Ten-dollar price range, first half.
Gotgan...
sold 1,173.80 dollars.
(Gotgan, 1st half, Sales: 1,173.80 dollars)
The Star In My Heart...
sold 786.40 dollars.
(The Star In My Heart, 1st half, Sales: 786.40 dollars)
The result of Round Two...
will reflect the ratings on the sales.
Customer ratings. The Star In My Heart, 4.5.
(The Star In My Heart, Customer ratings, 4.5)
Gotgan.
Customer ratings, 2.6.
(Gotgan, Customer ratings, 2.6)
(Gotgan sold 1,173.80 dollars. The Star In My Heart ratings, 4.5)
(Their sales and customer ratings have diverged.)
Have you tried fried ginseng?
It goes really well with beer.
Hello. What do men love?
Here is the total result. Gotgan...
(Gotgan, The Star In My Heart)
sold 962.52 dollars.
The Star In My Heart...
sold 943.68 dollars.
In the first half, Gotgan has won.
(Gotgan wins.)
(But with 18.84 dollars difference only.)
"I should've sold five more."
That was the only thought that came to my mind.
(Number One)
I've been to many events recently.
- You do many pop-up stores, right?
- Yes.
Did you bring the cutting board too?
Yes, I custom-made it.
That's crazy.
(The opponent is wary of Number One from the start.)
Ninth place, Number One.
Select your opponent.
(Round 1, 9th place, Kwak Dong Hoon of Number One)
I have a feeling this will be their strong suit.
Right.
He's gone to the beer festival...
last year too, so he knows how it's like.
That's cool.
- He must be good.
- You can't beat someone like that.
He smirked as soon as he heard the mission.
I thought this would become my main stage.
Number One has selected...
Koony.
- Which one?
- Koony.
Which restaurant is Koony?
- Which?
- Who?
- Kony?
(Still lacks awareness, Lee Sung Hoon of Koony)
I selected them...
because I thought they were as unpopular as us.
Thank you.
I think they'll get a lot more popular.
Right. They're cool.
- Seriously.
- The bandanas.
We underdogs will fight each other...
to the best of our abilities.
An underdog against an underdog.
It's actually better this way.
Whether we reveal our faces or not...
Whether it's a blind competition or not...
We'll reveal our faces.
We won't make it a blind competition.
Let us uncover our faces and breathe in fresh air.
I was confident.
I've participated in a lot of pop-ups and beer festivals.
I've worked on-site,
so I was confident.
I've participated in...
a lot of beer festivals.
I know how things work there...
better than everyone else.
We've probably done more hands-on battles than them.
I think we know better what sells...
and what doesn't.
If you ask me which teams I want to avoid until the end,
they are Number One and Koony.
It's a strong team against a strong team.
The king of Busan versus the king of Yeonnam-dong.
(The underdogs match)
(The strongest-at-festivals match)
(Number One)
You look cool.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Black suits you.
- You look cool too.
When will we show ourselves?
You look cool.
Since we're revealing our faces,
I thought the visual impact was important.
That's why we wore the cowboy hats.
- Your hats look cool.
- Thank you.
Good luck.
- Thank you, Chef.
- Thank you.
This must be fried bossam.
Yes, we're making braised pork belly.
You cut them nicely.
The concept of our first-half menu...
is "An Express Trip to Shanghai."
We prepared egg noodles, braised pork belly,
and chili shrimp.
We wanted to introduce various dishes...
to the customers all in one set...
at the beer festival.
Rather than preparing a single menu, it'd be better to prepare...
a variety of dishes.
(A cost-effective set menu)
(A Trip to Shanghai, 18 dollars)
(Egg noodles, braised pork belly, chili shrimp)
(Kwak Dong Hoon, Lee Sung Hoon's opponent)
Jae Beom and I will put on a performance...
focused on showmanship to make the dish.
Eighteen dollars.
- Number One versus Koony.
- Tacos.
I knew someone would choose tacos.
Tacos would sell well with beer.
I think it'll sell well.
For the first half, we prepared the original Mexican tacos.
(Authentic Mexican tacos)
We chose Mexican tacos...
because we could do a performance with it.
(A huge griddle)
(Wood cutting board)
There will be a burning oil pot,
and I'll strike down hard on the meat with a big knife...
as a performance.
I'll stir-fry it on the griddle and let the smell spread too.
To the left, 3cm.
No, 3cm to the right.
My nose is bleeding.
This mission must be very tough.
When you did all the hard work.
It's done.
This is the street vibe.
(Best beer snack, authentic tacos, 5 pieces in 1 plate, 18 dollars)
(Performance-focused)
(Impressive showmanship)
Why?
Are we the only ones wearing stuff like this?
I'm Chili Kwak.
I'm Song-brero.
Song-brero.
(A Trip to Shanghai by Lee Sung Hoon...)
(versus Authentic Mexican Tacos by Kwak Dong Hoon)
The first half of business begins now.
Let's do this.
(Kwak Dong Hoon places himself at the outdoor stand.)
- Welcome.
- Hello.
(He immediately starts cutting.)
(This...)
(They both react to the customers' voices.)
Welcome.
(Which restaurant will the first group choose?)
- This is a set.
- It's a set.
(Lee Sung Hoon, 1 order)
- It looks good.
- Yes.
- An order coming in.
- Thank you.
(And immediately after)
Feel free to ask anything.
What are you selling?
We sell those three.
Chili shrimp, braised pork belly, and egg noodles.
Did you see the orders?
Yes. I'm keeping an eye on them.
- Looks like we get all 3.
- There are 3 dishes.
(Lee Sung Hoon, 2 orders)
- It's cheap.
- It is.
I thought it was 18 dollars for 1 dish.
(Lee Sung Hoon, 3 orders)
Isn't it a good deal if we get three dishes?
(Lee Sung Hoon, 4 orders)
Do we get all 3 for 18 dollars?
I don't think so.
You get all 3 for 18 dollars.
- Really?
- Yes.
I deep-fried braised pork belly to save time.
I boiled the sauce separately...
and made it thicker than usual.
You can enjoy 3 dishes at 18 dollars,
which is cost-effective.
Hello.
(Koony, 7 orders)
Try A Trip to Shanghai.
We need both, right?
Here you go.
(Lee Sung Hoon of Koony, egg noodles)
- Why?
- Turns out I like this stuff.
- This is so good.
- Yes.
- The portion is big.
- It is.
I want to go give them a thumbs up.
Hello.
(Chili Kwak next door)
Let's make this fun.
- When a customer passes by, - Hello.
I strike the cutting board with my knife.
Hello.
When customers hang around to see what it is,
I stir-fry a lot of meat on the griddle...
so they can smell it.
(Stimulating the sense of smell)
Hello.
- How do I order?
- You can use the kiosk.
Okay.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, 1 order)
(Another group of customers approach next.)
The sausages look so good.
(They saw the meat boiling in the oil pot.)
- Please confirm your order.
- I'm hungry.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, 2 orders)
(The sound of the knife hitting the cutting board)
(Customers are drawn to it.)
What's in the tacos?
We have pork tacos,
and the Mexican sausages are called chorizo.
- To pay.
- Please confirm your order.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, 4 orders)
Tacos. They look delicious.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, 6 orders)
At one point, we got a lot of customers.
Hello.
- Jae Beom, orders incoming.
- Okay.
First, grill the meat...
until it turns golden-brown.
Then boil it in oil.
It's a method to boil the meat to become like suyuk.
It has a very gamey smell...
and taste.
The meat is so cool.
Next, I prepare chorizo, Mexican sausages.
I'll prepare the salsa sauce.
It tastes strongly of chilies and tomatoes.
I'll torch the vegetables.
The scorched-like smoky flavor is added to the sauce.
I'll grind them using a blender.
The sauce tastes of vegetables,
along with the strong touch of chilies and tomatoes.
That's my salsa sauce.
(Finishing it off with salsa, cilantro, and onions)
Tacos.
Enjoy.
Enjoy your food.
(Number One, Koony)
Currently, the sales difference between Koony and Number One...
in the 18-dollar price range is just 1 plate.
What?
One plate difference.
Goodness.
(Smiling in disbelief)
You get unlimited nachos refills, so come back when you finish it.
- Really? That's amazing.
- Thank you.
You get unlimited nachos refills, so come back when you finish it.
We will give them a beer snack for free.
I prepared seasoned nachos as unlimited refills.
(Unlimited nachos refill)
It's very cheap to cut and deep-fry...
tortilla ourselves.
(Adding handmade seasoning to fried nachos)
It's only for those who order tacos.
Unlimited.
For the duration of their stay at the festival,
they could continuously come to my booth.
Do we get unlimited nachos if we buy tacos?
Yes, unlimited refills. Get it refilled 100 times.
- Really? Nachos?
- Yes. It's delicious.
- I came for more nachos.
- Okay.
- More nachos, please.
- Coming.
Hello.
Enjoy.
How many tacos? One?
Please confirm your order.
(A new order has been placed.)
(Number One, Koony)
Hello. Come and try the delicious Shanghai set.
Just focus on my tasks.
We were neck and neck.
We could catch up with just a little push.
The nachos are refillable. Come back if you need more.
Thank you. Enjoy your food.
Enjoy.
Thanks for the order.
Hello, thank you.
In the 1st half of the 18-dollar price range,
Number One has won.
(Kwak Dong Hoon, 1,386 dollars, Lee Sung Hoon, 1,231.92 dollars)
As I thought.
(The first half result: Gotgan wins, The Star In My Heart loses)
(Number One wins, Koony loses)
(If it becomes a 1:1 draw,)
(the winner will be decided by the customer ratings.)
The second half will begin soon. Please get ready.
(The second half will decide the winners.)
Street Beer Festival!
Just kill me.
It's not over yet.
I... The banner... Where did one go?
Only 30 minutes before the 2nd half starts?
I can't do this.
I'm worried.
It all comes down to who sends out the dishes faster.
I'll keep them coming as fast as I can.
(Sighing)
(The 2nd half of the 18-dollar price range)
(Number One's mala skewers versus Koony's American Street Food Box)
Number One's mala skewers look good,
but the queue is too long.
Do you mean the order queue?
The queue to order is already long.
(Both teams have a long queue.)
- What?
- Please confirm your order.
It's 18 dollars for 20.
It's very cost-effective.
Is the portion big?
- Please confirm your order.
- It's those.
I see.
They opened one at Bupyeong Station, and it's so good.
Take it.
For the second half,
we're selling mala skewers.
(Mala skewers)
Mala skewers are one...
of the most trending foods nowadays.
It's mala skewers.
- What?
- Mala skewers.
- Where?
- Over there.
- I told you it was mala skewers.
- It's mala.
I told you just now. They sell 8 for 20 dollars or something.
- Or 15 dollars.
- I need to try it.
(The desire hunter competes with the popular food.)
Eighteen-dollar price range.
Number One is leading Koony by one plate.
(Current sales count: Number One, 18, Koony, 17)
- What's the difference?
- One plate.
I kept sighing.
Tae Hee, tell them about fishcake every now and then.
Tae Hee, tell them about fishcake...
- every now and then.
- Okay.
We prepared an assortment of different street foods.
(Garlic shrimp noodles, potato wedges, guacamole, hot dog)
(Pulled pork: Southern American style barbecue...)
(which is shredded along the grain.)
(And...)
(Fishcake)
I thought it'd be cold during the second half.
So I prepared fishcakes as the hidden free menu.
(The fishcake broth has been boiling since the first half.)
Tae Hee, let's carry the broth together.
Watch out.
(They placed the fishcakes, their secret weapon, in front.)
When the steam rises...
in the lighting in the evening,
the sight alone catches your eyes.
You don't expect...
American Street Food Box and fishcakes to go well together.
But I think this is what makes festivals fun.
I guess the hidden free menu is the fishcakes.
- Did you take your fishcake?
- No.
It's on the house.
- Really? Thank you.
- Yes.
Some even bought the menu...
to eat the fishcake.
Do you sell just the fishcakes?
We don't.
It's complimentary for those who order from us.
You can take one each after buying our food.
It's a good idea to give out something with soup.
I'm glad they gave out fishcakes.
- Sorry?
- I'm glad they gave out fishcakes.
You need warm soup like this.
How are you?
(Number One)
The stall next to us gives out fishcakes.
Where do I get unlimited popcorn? Will you give it here?
- Popcorn...
- Once you finish it,
bring back the empty plate, and I'll refill it.
You don't give out nachos anymore, do you?
I'll give you some popcorn instead.
Thank you.
We're using the same strategy as the first half.
I prepared unlimited mala popcorn.
(Mala popcorn against fishcakes)
Mala popcorn? They give popcorn.
It's 20 skewers.
They give mala popcorn too.
Popcorn too?
I think they give us 30 of it.
Enjoy.
(Current sales count: 30 for both teams)
(Pouring)
- Thank you, enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Sung Hoon, refill coleslaw.
- Okay.
(The order sheets pour out nonstop.)
It's sold out?
Is it sold out if the kiosk says so?
- Does it say sold out?
- Yes.
The kiosk says we're sold out.
- Yes, I cut it off.
- Is it right?
We have too many orders.
Is it not sold out?
We have a lot of orders backed up,
so we can accept only until here. I'm sorry.
I couldn't handle it.
They cut off their orders, right?
- Did they stop?
- What?
They're not doing anything.
A mental breakdown...
No. They couldn't be ready for the dishes.
They're having trouble keeping up with making the dishes.
I heard them saying, "We need to stop the orders."
"We need to stop accepting orders."
You can move quickly...
when things run smoothly.
But they were moving very slowly.
Like this.
I thought, "They're clearly having a mental breakdown."
How many orders should we accept?
What? Until the round ends.
(1 order)
For us, we kept getting orders.
It felt like they had stopped.
Eighteen-dollar price range.
Currently, Number One...
is ahead of...
Koony.
(Current sales count: Number One, 50, Koony, 35)
Okay, let's do this.
You can do it.
- We didn't have enough food...
- You can do it.
to serve right away.
(Checking the remaining meat)
Even if we need to stop taking in orders for a bit,
I should secure as much food as possible.
That was what I thought.
(Menu replenishment status: Guacamole)
(Menu replenishment status: Hawaiian garlic shrimp noodles)
Tae Hee, give them a lot of shrimps.
- Tae Hee, potatoes are ready.
- Okay.
(Menu replenishment status: Potato wedges)
Sung Hoon, is pulled pork ready?
Meat? I'll give it to you.
- Give them a lot.
- Call their numbers.
Yes. Give them a lot.
(The lacking dishes have been replenished.)
Undo the sold-out status.
(Lee Sung Hoon resumes the business.)
Okay, "Street Food Box."
- Let's go.
Please confirm your order.
- Are you giving it right away?
- Yes, you can take it now.
- Take a fishcake and soup each.
- Thank you.
You can order now.
Give them a lot.
Thank you for waiting so long.
It's the perfect time to eat.
Right, it's about time you crave supper.
Let me close it for you.
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thank you. I'll enjoy the food.
Thank you. Enjoy.
All orders will be closed after 15 minutes.
(Meanwhile, Kwak Dong Hoon has been processing orders nonstop.)
Why isn't it decreasing?
- What isn't?
- The number of orders.
You just need to do 35 more. The ongoing ones.
I've done 33 so far.
You can do it.
The second half was a nightmare.
The number of plates I've made throughout the nightmare...
and the number of orders left to process were the same.
It should end as you work on it.
(Current sales status: 68)
(Orders which need to be processed: 35)
There's no end to this.
(What's the result of the order rush?)
Let's do our best for the second half as well.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
(The 2nd half of 10-dollar price range starts.)
People have already lined up in front of our stall.
Oh, no.
Nice.
I'm going to be generous with the cutlassfish bones, Mom.
Let's give them more than enough.
Since cutlassfish bones are a by-product, they're cheap.
They can be used to increase the quantity.
We'd be able to make them in bulk.
They're the perfect simple snack to have with beer for dinner.
(Spring mugwort wasabi mayo sauce)
Cutlassfish on top.
We're placing boneless cutlassfish sticks on top.
(Deep-fried Jeju silver cutlassfish)
(Gotgan)
(Jeju silver cutlassfish fritters and crispy fish bones)
The cutlassfish fritters sound good.
Cutlassfish is already flavorful,
so deep-frying it would intensify the taste.
- This looks good.
- It's cutlassfish.
(The menu customers were excited about even before opening)
(Thanks to it, there's a long line at Gotgan.)
(Gotgan)
We have an order.
(10 dollars)
(The orders come in one after the other.)
Okay, the orders are here.
(Plating the cutlassfish bone fritters first)
Here, Mom. Let's place five pieces of cutlassfish on top of each.
- Five each?
- Yes, five each.
(Warm boneless cutlassfish fritters after being deep-fried again)
Number 1060, please!
(Gotgan has started serving customers.)
The batter.
The line outside is no joke.
I bet we'll sell like crazy.
Let's go.
(The line at the next-door booth is just as long.)
Enjoy.
Hi.
It's cold, isn't it? Gosh.
- This is my first order.
- Is that so?
Please enjoy this warm stew.
It's the perfect menu for this weather.
- Right?
- Yes.
Since the weather has gotten cold, it's time for the soup.
It's cold.
Shouldn't there be warm food in the second half?
Like soup.
They're selling jjamppong soft tofu stew.
It's perfect for warming up.
There are so many lines somewhere else.
I'm sure you were craving soup now that it's gotten cold.
(The Star In My Heart)
(Half perilla and half jjamppong soft tofu stew)
For the soft tofu, we got fresh soy milk from a tofu place,
turned the heat off once the soy milk came to a boil,
and stirred it for 15 minutes after pouring in some coagulant.
(House-made soft tofu made from fresh soy milk)
(Perilla soft tofu)
(Jjamppong soft tofu)
- Welcome.
(Served half and half)
Please wait a little. It won't take long.
- Oh, my.
- Hi.
You brought the crown.
Welcome.
We took a strategic approach.
As it's a beer festival,
we felt the need to prepare props, such as balloons and crowns,
for customers to decorate themselves.
"What? Where did they get that?"
Our strategy was to make the customers wonder.
(During the first half)
Leave with a crown after you order a dish!
The must-have item at festivals!
Social butterflies need one.
- Of course. Thank you.
- Right?
Thank you.
Be the queen of the day.
(While also promoting the first-half menu)
If you bring this back in the second half,
you'll get something good with the soft tofu.
Our strategy was to provide...
twice as many fritters in the jjamppong soft tofu stew...
if the customers came back with the crown in the second half.
- You'll get more food at dinner.
- Thank you.
You have to come for dinner.
There are too many choices in the Street Arena.
Increase the number of returning customers.
That was today's strategy.
A crown!
I didn't know so many people would return with the crown.
Crispy topping. Enjoy.
Enjoy.
- Should we double the jjamppong?
- Double it.
- Double the jjamppong?
- You're the best.
- Okay.
- Goodness, CEO Jo.
- The best.
You came by earlier, right?
I couldn't order...
- because it was sold out.
- I know.
I felt bad.
Welcome.
- Where's your crown?
- Oh, right. It's over there.
You lost it after some drinks, didn't you?
Really?
I always remember the faces...
- Really?
- of people I've seen.
It's just part of my daily life.
I worked hard to pay more attention...
to each and every customer.
Enjoy. Bye.
Welcome.
Thank you. Enjoy.
(10 dollars)
(The Star In My Heart, 32 orders)
Hi.
(The Star In My Heart, 37 orders)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It'll be right up. Give me a second.
(The Star In My Heart prepares each order as it comes in.)
- Number 2139.
- That's fast.
Number 2139.
I'm naturally fast.
- Number 0603.
- Lots of green onion, please.
Lots of green onion.
Here, enjoy.
(It may be fritters, but Gotgan is serving them fast.)
(The Star In My Heart, Gotgan)
(Current total orders)
This is from Jeju Island.
Take one.
- Enjoy.
- Give me a minute.
Please take one if you need it.
Enjoy.
- The food was great.
- Thank you.
- Was it good?
- Yes.
I'm relieved.
- It was amazing.
- The ingredients weren't frozen,
- so it tasted better.
- I see.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Bye.
While leaving, our customers said,
"It was delicious!"
Hearing them say they enjoyed the meal made me happy.
(They received harsh reviews in the first half.)
It's so good.
Having cutlassfish fritters like this is a first.
- It's good.
- Totally.
It's not something I could try even on Jeju Island.
(Crunchy)
- The bone fritter is amazing.
- The bone fritter is good.
- Let me try it.
- The fritters are delicious.
- Try it.
- Go ahead.
It's the perfect beer snack.
- It doesn't make you full.
- Exactly.
(Gotgan's second-half menu is a hit.)
- It's good.
- For real.
- Mom, how's the next booth doing?
- What?
- The booth next to ours.
- There's a line.
There isn't any soup around here.
So our soup is selling well.
- Perilla.
- Excuse me.
- Is it boiling hot?
- Yes.
All good. Go ahead.
- I'll boil another batch.
- In the ten-dollar price range...
(In the 10-dollar price range)
The Star In My Heart...
is leading by ten dollars against Gotgan.
(Cheering)
- From earlier?
- It was delicious.
Was it? Thank you.
Enjoy. Thank you. Bye.
Number 3295.
(The Star In My Heart's orders: 68, Gotgan's orders: 68)
(Gotgan's orders: 69)
In the ten-dollar price range,
Gotgan is leading by ten dollars...
- against The Star In My Heart.
- Yes.
By ten dollars?
(A neck-and-neck battle)
- What's your number?
- I just came to thank you.
Thank me?
I really appreciate that you came over.
Thank you.
- Did you have some beer?
- Yes.
No wonder your face looks flushed.
I'm jealous. Enjoy.
- Welcome.
- It'll be right up.
- Don't forget to dip it here.
This is our special soy sauce.
Jae Beom, can we get more jjamppong base?
- This is all that we have.
- Okay.
- Even the perilla, right?
- Yes.
Hold on. I'm so sorry. I'm afraid...
we're sold out.
I'm sorry. We're sold out.
(Current time)
(Meanwhile, Gotgan is still busy.)
Let's go. Let's get on with the second half.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Enjoy.
(Jo Seo Hyung of The Star In My Heart)
We're done.
When we looked around after announcing we were sold out,
the line was super long.
(Jo Seo Hyung sold out first.)
We wouldn't sell as many as them.
I was very anxious after selling out.
Let's do it.
We can do it.
What ingredients do we have left?
Ingredients...
(We don't have any ingredients.)
Pork belly.
What could we make with it?
Hold on.
Get a grip, Seo Hyung.
I should cook the food...
that the customers want, not what I want.
Finding out what the customers wanted...
and cooking it as quickly as possible seemed right.
What would you like?
- I'll cook what you'd like.
- Soup.
- Something with soup?
- Yes.
A freshwater shrimp soup-style...
spicy sujebi.
- And warm.
- I'm in for spicy.
- Spicy and warm?
- Yes.
I'll take 15 customers starting now.
We will sell a limited number of 15 spicy sujebi starting now!
Give me a minute.
Spring onions and two potatoes.
(Bought more ingredients after gathering customers)
- Did you open up 15 orders?
- Yes.
Please pour in the water and start boiling it.
Okay. Right at this moment.
Gosh.
- It looks good.
- I boiled it...
with a bunch of kuruma shrimp.
(New menu: Kuruma shrimp sujebi)
Try a bit of the soup first...
since you waited a while.
- It's good.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- I'll start serving.
It's limited.
Get in line, and you might get a bowl.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
The end. It's empty now.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- All done.
- Did we sell another 15?
- Yes, it was 15.
The other team is sold out,
- so they're making something else.
- What?
The other team is sold out, so they're selling something else.
Let's turn the tables right now.
Wouldn't it be upsetting...
if they caught up to us now?
Let's sell a few more if possible.
- Let's start the double event.
- Okay.
- How many do we have left?
- A total of 116.
A total of 116?
Come and have some boneless cutlassfish fritters!
We'll be serving double portions!
Starting now, the next ten customers will receive double portions!
Ten customers!
- They said double.
- Is it served right away?
- Yes.
- Yes, as soon as you order.
(10 dollars)
- Did you order?
- Yes.
The food is served...
- as soon as you order.
- Only ten orders...
of boneless cutlassfish with double portions are left. Come try it.
(More orders come in thanks to the double event.)
What a generous amount.
- Enjoy.
All orders will be closed...
after 15 minutes.
(15 minutes until last orders)
Close the orders?
- They said there are 15 minutes.
- About 15 minutes?
(Last order time is based on kiosk orders.)
What else are you feeling like eating?
Why? Are there more?
Because I'm not drinking at the moment,
I'm wondering what you're craving right now.
- Something spicy.
- Spicy?
- What a legend.
- Spicy. Something really spicy.
How does spicy stir-fried pork belly sound?
- I'm in.
- Amazing.
Who's craving spicy stir-fried pork belly?
- Pork belly!
- Who's craving spicy...
- Sir, how's my food?
- A top star chef!
A top star chef? Give me a minute.
I'll take five orders.
- Hurry.
- Should I go?
Five?
- Amazing.
- She's great.
- She's the business queen.
- For real.
- She's good.
- That's how you do business.
Her goal is to sell at least one more dish if possible.
Cool.
How many minutes are left? My strength show is about to begin.
The customers want spicy stir-fried pork belly.
I'd rather die than go home.
Seven.
(Additional grocery purchase: 26 dollars)
- Let's go.
- I'll show you what I can cook.
Here it comes. Come on.
You're all going into the dish.
Come have some boneless cutlassfish.
It's buy 1, get 1 free.
Grilled Jeju cutlassfish.
We must win.
Going home now is absurd.
We have to win.
We must return after surviving.
Buy 1, get 1 free, so a total of 2.
(Who won the 10-dollar price range match?)
Go and have a glass of beer right now.
Seung Jae, let's get to the finals.
I'm always all about winning.
(15-dollar price range)
We came in 1st in Round 1.
We're not about losing,
so we will advance.
First place, The Sauce.
Select your rival restaurant.
I choose Wolfie's.
We both cook Western cuisine,
and I grew up watching him cook,
which is why I chose him.
(1st of Round 1, Choi Sang Hyun,)
(chooses 13th of Round 1, Lee Jae Hoon.)
I've been chosen.
I rarely post about...
how good a restaurant is other than mine...
on my social media.
Chef Lee visited out of the blue...
and left a post saying our food was great.
I'd feel a sense of pride...
if I beat Chef Lee Jae Hoon.
He's practically a first-generation wine bar chef.
Since I'm also running a wine bar,
I followed in his footsteps.
In a way, our cuisine overlaps.
(The two are walking the same path.)
If I'm being frank,
from what I see,
they chose us thinking we're a weak team.
They chose the team they considered the weakest.
Wolfie's lacks the variety compared to the others.
I'd be happy with them too.
Wolfie's.
I will make them regret...
choosing us as their first opponent.
Although we are much younger chefs,
it won't be easy for you, Chef Lee.
Experience the nerve-racking feeling...
of a junior pulling ahead.
(15-dollar price range wine dining generation match)
(1st-half: The Sauce, 872.10 dollars versus Wolfie's, 774 dollars)
(The Sauce: Won, Wolfie's: Lost)
Enjoy. Thank you.
Please come get your dish once your number is called.
(And the second half has started.)
Coincidentally, our Round Two menu...
overlapped to the point that it was unbelievable.
(Before business started)
(Glancing over)
Chef, is that dessert?
- Is it a mango dessert?
- Yes.
We're serving mango sauce...
while the other team is serving mango for dessert.
We're both using crispy chili peppers.
Which dish are you using the crispy chili peppers for?
- We're also using them.
- Exactly.
Both teams are serving deep-fried chicken and pork belly.
(Both are deep-fried dishes.)
But food is similar yet different.
If we serve what we prepared well,
we can definitely win.
The second dish is the forbidden witch chicken.
After deep-frying chicken drumsticks,
they're seasoned...
with a spicy blend of spices.
Next, they're mixed with crispy chili pepper chips.
A refreshing mango sauce is served on the side.
Anyone will love the dish.
We brought our killer dish for the second half.
Our second-half dish is...
deep-fried pork belly and fruit jelly.
Deep-frying the pork belly so that it doesn't get soggy...
even with the sauce was our biggest goal.
Our sauce is closer to...
Thai-style seasoned fried chicken.
It's refreshing.
We've got the upperhand against the mango sauce.
A surprising number of customers wanted dessert.
So we prepared a refreshing dessert, a fruit jelly.
(Deep-fried pork belly, handmade mango jelly)
It's deep-fried against deep-fried.
It's mango and chips versus mango and chips.
Right. It's mango and chips versus mango and chips.
I am curious about the result of this match.
(Deep-fried, mango, and chili)
(Same-ingredient showdown)
Enjoy. The chili peppers aren't spicy, so enjoy them together.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy. Thank you.
(The customer ordered both from The Sauce and Wolfie's.)
Give me a minute. There's always space.
Is this a same-ingredient showdown with these chili peppers?
They look the same.
The ingredients are the same.
- Chili peppers and mango.
- Can the ingredients overlap...
this much?
- This must be mango dipping sauce.
- I'm curious about the chicken.
It smells of mango.
How is it?
(Lee Jae Hoon's forbidden witch chicken)
Is it spicy?
- It's sweet.
- This is the perfect beer snack.
Is it?
- Was this deep-fried pork belly?
- Yes.
(Choi Sang Hyun's deep-fried pork belly)
It reminds me of guobaorou.
- It's good.
- Right?
Which did you like the most?
I liked the deep-fried pork belly the most.
Same here.
It was a dish that I had never tried before.
(Another customer ordered the deep-fried pork belly.)
Okay.
I won't need this because of the container.
Coriander with deep-fried pork belly is a first.
(Choi Sang Hyun's deep-fried pork belly)
- It's good.
- The meat is tender.
It tastes Chinese.
It's giving off tangsuyuk vibes.
At festivals, the food...
may lack detail...
as it's made in bulk.
- True.
- But not these,
- since they are made by chefs.
- Totally.
- The food is all great.
- Exactly.
The chili peppers aren't spicy, so enjoy them together.
- Whose number has been called?
- Number 5127.
- Enjoy.
- Here's the sauce.
- Did your number get called?
- Enjoy.
(Current revenues: 540 dollars versus 490 dollars)
Did you get the text message?
(The gap gradually widens.)
Here's for 0218.
We must win. Losing isn't an option for us.
I have a feeling...
we'll win the second half.
Is it done now?
Yes.
We have to adjust the portions now.
No.
(Crowded)
There are so many customers.
Keep frying them.
No, I meant the pork belly.
How much do we have? Is that it?
Yes.
(The pork belly is already running low.)
Selling these should be more than enough.
The other team can't sell more than us.
In the 15-dollar price range,
The Sauce and Wolfie's...
are tying in revenue.
This is bad, Seung Jae.
If we're currently tied...
- Us?
- Yes.
I'll hurry.
(Checking the other team)
I'll fry the drumsticks fast.
How many minutes left?
A lot. We have more than 30 minutes left.
- More than 30 minutes?
- Yes.
As there was still a lot of time left...
and I could see the other team...
continuously deep-frying...
Go get some pork belly.
We had no choice...
but to keep going.
Let's close the orders for now.
(Orders closed)
- Do you have pork belly?
- Yes, over there.
I'll buy three for now.
(35.10 dollars deducted for pork belly purchase)
- How much was each?
- It was 11.70 dollars.
Fry them for now, okay?
How long will it take, Seung Jae?
It's coming up.
Open the order, please.
(Orders closed)
(Orders resume)
How many more can we serve?
Seven, eight...
We have one portion left.
- One more?
- We've got one more left.
We're about to get one order, so he'd be the last, right?
Yes.
Chef, from now on,
- we could deep-fry pork galbi...
- Yes?
and serve that with French fries.
Got it.
Aren't they sold out? Yes, they are.
Ma'am, the fried chicken is sold out.
But we're now selling deep-fried pork galbi.
Think of it as deep-fried...
- pork galbi skewers.
- Skewers?
- Yes, it's good.
- Is that so?
- Would you like one?
- Yes.
Got it. Please place an order.
(Pork galbi, the first half ingredient)
"How many more are left? How many more can we sell?"
That was all I could think about.
Change it to cumin pork, please.
- Cumin pork?
- Yes.
They're selling the skewers from earlier now.
The other team kept on deep-frying things.
We have another deep-fried pork galbi.
Got it.
Should we buy another pack of pork belly?
- I'll get it.
- Okay.
We were up to our necks as if being chased with a hammer.
We took a step back to take two steps forward.
We went and bought pork belly that was 12 to 15 dollars,
cooked it up, and served three orders.
Enjoy.
- We can make deep-fried pork galbi.
- Okay.
The chili peppers aren't spicy,
- so enjoy them together.
- Okay.
The chili peppers aren't spicy, so enjoy them together.
- It's cumin skewers. Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Enjoy. Have a great time.
Have some deep-fried pork belly! There are only six left!
Come have some skewers! Deep-fried skewers!
- Double the portion!
- One last order left!
(The result of the 1st half: 1 to 0)
In the second half,
The Sauce sold 1,581.31 dollars...
and Wolfie's sold 1,344.60 dollars.
The Sauce has won.
(The Sauce: Won, Wolfie's: Lost)
The second half has ended.
Here are the results of Round Two.
(Round 2: 1-on-1 same-price battle)
Number One and Koony.
Please come up to the stage.
(The festival's strongest underdog matchup)
In the first half, Number One won.
(First-half result)
(If Number One wins again, they advance to Round 3.)
Though we may have won by a hair,
it's still a win.
I kept praying.
"Please let us advance."
They are great businessmen in the first place.
Both are great businessmen.
In the second half.
Number One.
The final total...
is 984.96 dollars.
Koony.
(Koony's second half result)
The final total...
(Revenue times customer ratings)
(Number One, the 2nd half, 984.96 dollars)
is 1,272.24 dollars.
In the second half, Koony won,
making it a 1-to-1 tie.
(In the second half, Koony won.)
(Number One versus Koony, 1:1)
Gosh, it's 1-to-1? It's the customer ratings.
What a bloodbath.
(In a tied situation, the team with the higher customer ratings wins.)
I had confidence,
but the result was unpredictable.
I kept thinking,
"I want to win. I want to advance to the next round."
The team to win with the higher customer ratings is...
Number One.
It's 3.7 points.
Koony.
(Average customer ratings of Number One are 3.7.)
It's 4.3 points.
The final winner of the 18-dollar price range is Koony.
(Koony is the final winner.)
- Well done.
- Great job.
- You too.
Koony won.
That team is amazing.
- Well done.
- You are cool.
You are so cool.
- Cool.
- It's nerve-racking.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
We've been making successful crowd-pleasing dishes.
Number One is a great team...
and has done well until now.
But our dishes pleased today's customers more.
- Well done.
- Good job.
What a bummer. I wanted to enjoy this more.
We should've provided better service.
Many of the mala skewers were cancelled near the end.
We're backed up and can't serve all the orders physically.
(Number One ended up getting orders cancelled.)
Customer ratings aren't solely based on taste.
Service is part of it.
I'm more of a businessman than a chef.
My main focus is on how to make dishes...
that will sell well to customers.
Regarding how the kitchen actually runs and such...
I realized many things...
including how much there is...
to learn.
Koony taught me a lot too.
Can we focus once we get back to work?
- We have to.
- This was fun.
(Number One: Lost, Koony: Won)
The Star In My Heart and Gotgan.
Please come up to the stage.
This one... It's unpredictable.
- Good luck.
- For real,
- I gave it my all.
- Same here.
- This match...
- It's a close one.
The son's apron...
(The aftermath of a fierce battle)
(1st-half revenue: 1,173.80 dollars, Customer ratings: 2.6)
(1st-half revenue: 789.40 dollars, Customer ratings: 4.5)
(Total revenue: 962.52 dollars versus 943.68 dollars)
(A 18.84 dollar difference in the 1st half)
In the first half, Gotgan has won.
(First-half result)
- A 20-dollar difference.
- It's a 20-dollar difference.
By a narrow margin.
In the second half,
Gotgan...
sold 1,300 dollars.
(Gotgan's 2nd half, Revenue: 1,300 dollars)
The Star In My Heart...
(Grocery expenses deducted)
sold 940.80 dollars.
(The Star In My Heart's 2nd half, Revenue: 940.80 dollars)
It'll depend on the customer ratings.
(The final total may change depending on the customer ratings.)
Customer ratings.
Gotgan.
It's 4.5 points.
(Gotgan's second half)
(Revenue: 1,300 dollars, Customer ratings: 4.5)
The Star In My Heart.
(The Star In My Heart's 2nd half, Revenue: 940.80 dollars)
It's 3.2 points.
The final winner of the 10-dollar price range is Gotgan.
(Gotgan is the final winner.)
- We did it.
- Congratulations.
- Well done.
- You did well.
Well done.
When I hugged my son after hearing that we won,
I was in total bliss.
I came with the thought of not returning after losing.
"I can go home relaxed with a win."
That was what crossed my mind.
We should've prepared more.
I guess the tofu wasn't all that good.
(Customer ratings of The Star In My Heart's 2nd half: 3.2)
(Impressed)
It's good.
- But it's quite salty...
- The perilla one is...
because it's one of the last bowls.
- What is it?
- It's good, but...
It's salty.
It was at the bottom of the caldron. We were one of the last customers.
It kind of tastes burnt.
Because it was near the bottom?
(The soft tofu is almost gone.)
Jae Beom, can we get more jjamppong base?
I had a small mental breakdown,
so I didn't season the menu well.
It didn't taste as good near the end...
as I wasn't meticulous enough.
(The Star In My Heart's customer ratings...)
(couldn't turn the tables around.)
I may have been cooking for 11 years,
but Chef Kim Mi Ryeong started from the basement of a market.
Just imagine how much she must've been through.
Watching her,
I realized no one could beat experience.
It hit me once again.
Business is a race against time.
- The survived nine teams, - Good job.
- please come up to the stage.
- Well done.
- We've returned from the pit.
- Literally.
- Well done.
- Good job.
There is 1 special rule in Round 2.
What rule?
What is it?
When it comes to business, customer ratings are...
an important index to determine the customers' return.
Among the eliminated teams,
the one with the highest customer ratings...
will receive a star pass...
- to enter Round Three.
- A star pass.
I guess one of them will move up.
- Among the eliminated teams?
- Yes.
Who has the highest customer ratings?
Who is it? I wonder who it is.
Among the eliminated teams, the one to survive...
with the highest customer ratings...
received 4.6 customer ratings.
It's Min's.
(Min's with 4.7 and 4.5 customer ratings)
- They nailed it.
- That's unbelievable.
- I'm going to slice the raw fish.
- That looks good.
There's a lot of raw fish in it.
- It's darn good.
- Yes.
- What about this?
- It's only five dollars. So cheap.
- How much is this?
- It's eight dollars.
In fact, there's so much raw fish in it.
Min's earned a chance...
- to enter Round Three.
- That's amazing.
You're crying.
Gosh.
It feels like...
I'm pulled up from the third basement floor.
We survived again like weeds.
- They continue to survive.
- I know.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
I finally feel better.
Come with us.
I can't believe I'm eliminated here.
All eight eliminated teams...
must close the restaurants immediately.
Many of the strong teams...
- got eliminated.
- I know.
All right.
Let's close it.
(Number One)
There's no end to learning.
I closed my restaurants many times before.
Even though I failed 25 times before,
it still wasn't easy to close it.
I don't cling to victory.
It would've been nice...
if we got to do something fun together for more.
It's sad that it ends here.
We're known for a low rate of business closure.
Business never goes as planned.
We prepared so much, but it didn't go as we planned.
It's so sad...
to have the restaurant go under and close it.
It's depressing.
I should've tried harder.
If I had put more effort, I wouldn't have had to close it.
It's heartbreaking.
- I think I was too proud.
- Bye.
It was very regrettable.
I'm kind of shocked.
A business closure is one of the experiences...
people don't have to go through.
It's kind of bitter.
Gosh.
Survivals are always bitter.
All eight closed teams...
must leave the Street Arena immediately.
Well done.
- Well done.
- Good work.
- I hope you win.
- Okay. Done.
Keep up the good work.
Good job.
- Sir.
- Oh, it's such a shame.
- Good job.
- It's such a shame.
Bye.
I have to change my name now.
I can't be a business genius anymore.
- Do your best.
- Good luck.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
The total revenue you made today is...
- How much is it?
- I think it's pretty high.
It's 39,494.56 dollars.
That's almost 40,000 dollars.
That's amazing.
So far, the total prize money...
(The 100,000 dollar prize money plus the revenue of Rounds 1 and 2)
is 161,183.16 dollars.
Hey.
It's 160,000 dollars.
Here is the mission for Round Three.
- Now?
- They're revealing it now?
The mission for Round Three is...
the 100 serving relay team match.
- It's a team match.
- Now, it's a real team match.
It's a real team match.
A team match is never predictable.
What does a 100 serving relay mean?
For this round, two restaurants will unite.
(100 serving relay team match)
The united team will sell two kinds of dishes in a relay.
(The united team will sell two different kinds of food in a relay.)
The first team must sell all 50 servings first...
in order for the second team to take over.
(The 1st team must sell 100 servings first for the 2nd team to start.)
The team that sells all 100 servings...
including the second team's 50 servings survives.
(The first team to sell all 100 servings will survive.)
One sells first, and the next team takes over.
Like a relay.
If the first team doesn't sell out, the next team can't even start?
Here is the commercial zone for Round Three.
Where is it going to be?
The commercial zone.
Oh, here it is.
- Where is it?
- What's that?
It looks like a park.
Isn't that the Olympic Park?
It's not a stadium.
- A garden.
- That's a fountain.
(A fountain?)
How are we supposed to know based on that?
- It's...
- It looks like Everland.
What?
Isn't that Everland? That's in Everland.
- Oh, you're right.
- With the flowers.
Isn't it the parade area?
This place has approximately 14,000 visitors a day.
It's an amusement park.
It's an amusement park?
It's been 2, 3 decades since I last visited an amusement park.
- Everland is tough.
- Should we focus on a family meal?
It's an amusement park.
Then it's mostly families.
There will be many kids in the amusement park.
This will be a blind round.
Then now, we will decide the united teams.
How?
The team with the highest customer ratings...
will choose the united team first.
We placed eighth. It's disappointing.
(8th, HunGry, 3.75)
We placed bottom in terms of the average customer ratings.
First place, Hohyunghojae.
Gather the team you want to work with.
Hohyunghojae placed first?
Oh, they got 4.55.
- Is anyone going to step forward?
- They're good...
Hohyunghojae is strong.
- You decide.
- What?
Think carefully.
Anyone who wants to team up with us, please come forward.
(They must choose from the applicants.)
What? No one's stepping forward.
Why?
Why are you coming?
- Seriously.
- We live close by.
- The three strongest left.
We only have elders?
Excuse me.
- No young people?
- Hang on. Elders?
How can you say that?
- Hohyunghojae.
- Are you saying we're old?
Name the restaurant you'd like to work with.
You choose.
They're discussing.
(7th, BokBok, 4.05)
(Star pass, Min's, 4.6)
The restaurant we'd like to work with is...
- Goal!
(Jung Ho Young and Hong Seok Cheon)
I look forward to working with you.
Let's pull it off.
Place your restaurant in the location you want...
on the commercial map.
- I'll let you choose.
- Yes. People walk from there...
It's the best here. Right?
- Nice.
- Instead of the entrance.
(Done choosing the restaurant location)
(Entrance, exit)
All five united teams are formed...
for Round Three.
(The united teams...)
(for the 100 serving relay team match are formed.)
I haven't been here for so long.
It's been so long.
I guess the tables are going to be here.
This is the front, right?
This is the front, and the customers will sit there.
(In the vast open amusement park,)
(new restaurants are now open.)
It's cute.
Good job on the Lulu Land.
- It looks nice.
- Yes.
One, two, three, four, five.
Wait.
Why are there six?
(Why are there six restaurants?)
One, two, three, four, five...
Oh, six.
- Six. What?
- Up there.
- Isn't it 5 teams?
- Why are there 6?
(5 teams entered Round 3, but there are 6 booths.)
Why is there one more spot?
Currently,
through the revival match,
- two teams survived.
- I knew it.
- Who is it?
I knew this was going to happen.
- Through there?
- Seriously.
Gosh.
(The revival match)
Good job.
I shouldn't have been so proud.
Good work.
Well done.
I'm craving soju.
I'm not even going to pee toward Songdo.
What's that?
Are we taking that to go home?
- That's mean.
- What the?
Is that a bus to underworld?
- This is depressing.
- What is that?
- Are we getting on that bus?
"A delicious restaurant shall return."
- Return?
I'm getting goosebumps.
- Awesome.
- We must return then.
"A delicious restaurant shall return."
(A delicious restaurant shall return.)
Yes. A delicious restaurant shall revive.
It's another chance.
Return? Come back?
There's still one more chance to survive.
(The consolation match)
(8 defeated restaurants)
(2nd place in Round 1, Lim Ki Hak)
(1,000 dollar sales in the shortest time, Jo Seo Hyung)
(Michelin Couple, Kim Hee Eun)
(The ultimate franchise owner, Kim Kwan Hoon)
(7th in Round 1, Shin Ga Young)
(Brand Predator, Kim Ho Yoon)
(Seochon crown prince, Lee Jae Hoon)
(Busan's best, Kwak Dong Hoon)
Isn't this a ghost bus?
It's never predictable.
This is cruel.
Where are they taking us?
(To Cheorwon)
(The last chance)
(Where is the battlefield of fate...)
(for the revival match?)
(Cheorwon)
(There are famous attractions with a long history.)
(Where magnificent nature...)
(and richness of life coexists.)
(Here, they'll be facing...)
(the last revival match.)
(A delicious restaurant shall return.)
It felt like I was being dragged somewhere.
I had a lot on my mind.
What's going to be there?
What kind of mission is going to torture me this time?
It seems everyone was holding each other in check.
They were whispering.
I could tell they were very anxious.
We're all rivals.
Someone's going to survive while others are eliminated.
- Cheorwon? Did you see that?
- See what?
Cheorwon?
It said Cheorwon and Pocheon.
If we're going to Cheorwon, are we going to an army camp?
- The food warehouse?
- That's my major. Class One?
We're both former army cooks.
So if we're going to an army camp,
and we get to use the army kitchen,
I'm thinking it'd be more advantageous for us.
I was expecting to serve...
random people in a rest stop or something.
We're entering the woods.
(People are making various speculations.)
Oh, we're here.
(Goseokjeong)
I think it's the flower garden.
Goseokjeong Flower Garden?
We're going to Goseokjeong.
(The place where 8 teams' fate relies on)
(The place where the dry wild land...)
(turns into a new sight)
(Goseokjeong Flower Garden)
(A famous attraction in Cheorwon which was a military training spot)
(Over 400,000 visitors comes here every September and October.)
Do we have to work out butt off in the flower garden?
It's our restaurant.
Where? Really?
They brought the X.
That's unbelievable. I don't know what to say.
(Exclaiming)
(Number One)
X...
That's unbelievable.
It was giving me PTSD.
It's traumatizing business owners.
There was an X on the shutter.
Who wouldn't be devastated?
What is this? Can you believe it?
This is crazy.
I can't even guess.
After losing in Round Two, your restaurants were...
closed.
However, we will give you the last chance.
The closure of your restaurants...
will be lifted temporarily.
(Closure lifted)
It's opening.
Hi.
The last chance to avoid the closure.
The revival match will begin.
I was excited. Let's try it again.
They're all rivals.
I was thinking about outdoing them.
I was happy. I'll get to enjoy cooking again today.
Tell me the mission already.
Here is the mission for the revival match.
- Where?
Are they going to open something? Or show the ingredient?
What is it?
There's a truck coming.
It's the wing truck.
- What's that?
- There must be something inside.
This is insane.
The five-ton wing truck.
- That's...
- What's going on?
I'm getting scared.
I never saw this coming.
What's inside?
Please.
Oh, my gosh.
"With rice."
There's so much rice.
(Cheorwon Odae Rice)
(A delicious restaurant shall return.)
"With rice?"
There's so much rice.
The topic of the revival match is Cheorwon Odae Rice.
- Is that it?
- Odae Rice.
I eat Odae Rice at home.
Each team must serve 100 customers...
a dish using rice or a dish that goes with rice.
Serve one dish per table...
which is a total of 20 dishes.
It's good rice.
Odae Rice is famous.
The customers today are reserved customers.
- What?
- Reserved customers.
- Please check the list...
of 100 people on the table.
- What?
- A list of 100 people?
There it is.
Who is it?
There are names inside.
Sixty eight...
Grandma Geum Ja.
Lee Gwang... Seventy two years old.
- They're quite old.
- They're old.
- They're elders.
The reserved customers are 100 ladies...
who have been eating Cheorwon Odae Rice for a long time.
They're elders.
(Rice and 100 ladies)
I'm hungry.
How should I target this?
Food for moms.
What does my mom like?
(Street Restaurant Fighter)
(What did I lack...)
(that made my restaurant close?)
(They must prove it...)
(with rice only.)
(I bought red underwear...)
(because I was told if I wore red underwear, I'd win.)
(I'll take everything for now.)
(Intense competition where no one yields)
(I failed to hide my expression.)
(You're so greedy.)
(A fierce competition is taking place.)
(Do you also sell a half size?)
(I don't have the rice cake machine.)
(Using all their strategies to survive)
(My boss went crazy.)
(We almost fried everything in the fridge.)
(I can't lose.)
(We have pride in our food.)
(Seize the palate of 100 people...)
(who cooked for their whole lives.)
(I don't like any food with artificial seasonings.)
(An objective bite...)
(and a cruel evaluation)
(- This is my favorite. - Not me.)
(It's not easy to go beyond...)
(their long years of standard.)
(The last chance...)
(to avoid the restaurant closure)
(Bet your all on your dish.)
(You failed to revive...)
(due to the lowest revenue.)
(That's mean.)
The restaurant that revived is...
(Who will be the last survivor of the brutal revival match?)